tslist.com 2016-07-16

# Privacy Policy - Camera Prive

Dark Media Group LLC (the “Company”) respects your privacy and is committed to protecting it through our compliance with this policy. This policy describes the types of information we may collect from you or that you may provide when you visit the website located at cameraprive.com (“Website”) and our practices for collecting, using, keeping, protecting, and disclosing that information. 

This policy applies to information we collect: 

  * On the Website (including desktop and mobile versions).
  * In email, text, and other electronic messages between you and the Website.
  * When you interact with our advertising and applications on third-party websites and services, if those applications or advertising include links to this policy.
  * When you interact with the Website through third-party social media platforms.

It does not apply to information collected by: 
  * us offline or through any other means, including on any other website operated by the Company or any third party (including our affiliates and subsidiaries); or
  * ny third party (including our affiliates and subsidiaries), including through any application or content (including advertising) that may link to or be accessible from (or on) the Website.

Please read this policy carefully to understand our policies and practices regarding your information and how we will treat it. If you do not agree with our policies and practices, your choice is not to use our Website. By accessing or using our Website, you agree to this policy and consent to our collection, use, disclosure, retention, and protection of your personal information as described in this policy. This policy may change on one or more occasions. We will consider your continued use of the Website after we make changes as your acceptance of the changes, so please check the policy frequently for updates. 

## 1\. Are minors welcome?

This Website is not intended for minors. You will only access the Website or register if you are at least 18-years old and have reached the age of majority in the country where you live. We prohibit all persons who do not meet the age requirements from accessing the Website. Minors must not access the Website or use its services. 

We do not knowingly collect any information about children, minors, or anyone under the age of majority. Nor do we knowingly market to children, minors, or anyone under 18-years old. If you are under 18-years old, we ask that you do not submit information to us. If we become aware that a child, minor, or anyone under 18-years old has registered with us and provided us with personal information, we will take steps to cancel that person’s registration. If we do cancel a registration because you breached our no minors rule, we may keep your email and IP address to make sure that you do not try to get around our rules by creating a new account. 

In accordance with 47 U.S.C. § 230(d), you are notified that parental control protections (including computer hardware, software, or filtering services) are commercially available that may assist in limiting access to material that is harmful to minors. You may find information about providers of these protections on the Internet by searching “parental control protection” or similar terms. If minors have access to your computer, please restrain their access to sexually explicit material by using any of the following products, which we provide for informational purposes only and do not endorse: [CYBERsitter™](http://www.cybersitter.com/) | [Net Nanny®](http://www.netnanny.com/) | [CyberPatrol](http://www.cyberpatrol.com/) | [ASACP](http://www.asacp.org/). 

## 2\. What types of information do we collect about you and how do we collect it?

We may collect several types of information from and about users of our Website or service, including information: 

  * by which you may be personally identified, including your name, mailing address, email address, telephone number, date of birth, government identification number/driver’s license number, tax identification number, bank account information, credit card information, or any other information that the Website collects that is defined as personal or personally identifiable information under law (“personal information”);
  * that is about you but individually does not identify you, including your age, gender, location, and any other optional information you provide about yourself; or
  * about your internet connection, the equipment you use to access our Website, and usage details.

We collect this information:   

  * Directly from you when you provide it to us.
  * Automatically as you navigate through the Website. Information collected automatically may include usage details, IP addresses, and information collected through cookies, web beacons, and other tracking technologies.
  * From third parties, for example, our business partners.

**Information You Provide to Us**

The information we collect on or through our Website may include: 

  * Information that you provide by filing in forms on our Website. This includes information provided at the time of registering to use our Website, purchasing services, or requesting further services. We may also ask you for information when you report a problem with our Website or service.
  * Records and copies of your correspondence (including email addresses), if you contact us.
  * Your responses to surveys that we might ask you to complete for research purposes.
  * Details of transactions you carry out through our Website and of the fulfillment of your requests. You may be required to provide financial information before placing an order through our Website or receiving payments from us.
  * Your search queries on the Website.

You also may provide information to be published or displayed (“posted”) on public areas of the Website, or transmitted to other users of the Website or third parties (collectively, “user contributions”). Your user contributions are posted on the Website and transmitted to others at your own risk. Additionally, we cannot control the actions of other users of the Website with whom you may choose to share your user contributions. Thus, we cannot and do not guarantee that your user contributions will not be viewed by unauthorized persons. 

**Information We Collect through Automatic Data Collection Technologies**

As you navigate through and interact with our Website, we may use automatic data collection technologies to collect certain information about your equipment, browsing actions, and patterns, including: 

  * Details of your visits to our Website, including traffic data, location data, logs, and other communication data and the resources that you access and use on the Website.
  * Information about your computer and internet connection, including your IP address, operating system, and browser type.

We also may use these technologies to collect information about your online activities over time and across third-party websites or other online services (behavioral tracking). 

The information we collect automatically is statistical data and does not include personal information, but we may keep it or associate it with personal information we collect in other ways or receive from third parties. It helps us to improve our Website and to deliver a better and more personalized service, including by allowing us to: 

  * Estimate our audience size and usage patterns.
  * Store information about your preferences, thus allowing us to customize our Website according to your individual interests.
  * Speed up your searches.
  * Recognize you when you return to our Website.

The technologies we use for this automatic data collection may include:   

  * **Cookies (or browser cookies)**. A cookie is a small file placed on the hard drive of your computer. You may refuse to accept browser cookies by activating the appropriate setting on your browser. But if you select this setting you may be unable to access certain parts of our Website. Unless you have adjusted your browser setting so that it will refuse cookies, our system will issue cookies when you direct your browser to our Website. If you want to learn more about cookies, please see [http://www.allaboutcookies.org](http://www.allaboutcookies.org/) or [http://www.youronlinechoices.eu](http://www.youronlinechoices.eu/). 
  * **Flash Cookies**. Certain features of our Website may use local stored objects (or Flash cookies) to collect and store information about your preferences and navigation to, from, and on our Website. Flash cookies are not managed by the same browser settings as are used for browser cookies. For information about managing your privacy and security settings for Flash cookies, you can access your Flash management tools from Adobe’s website.
  * **Web Beacons**. Pages of our Website (and our emails) may contain small electronic files known as web beacons (also referred to as clear gifs, pixel tags, and single-pixel gifs) that permit us, for example, to count users who have visited those pages (or opened an email) and for other related website statistics (for example, recording the popularity of certain website content and verifying system and server integrity). If you want to learn more about web beacons, please see <http://www.allaboutcookies.org/web-beacons/>.

We do not collect personal information automatically, but we may tie this information to personal information about you that we collect from other sources or you provide to us. 

**Third-party Use of Cookies and Other Tracking Technologies**

Some content or applications, including advertisements, on the Website are served by third parties, including advertisers, ad networks and servers, content providers, and application providers. These third parties may use cookies alone or in conjunction with web beacons or other tracking technologies to collect information about you when you use our Website. The information they collect may be associated with your personal information or they may collect information, including personal information, about your online activities over time and across different websites and other online services. They may use this information to provide you with interest-based (behavioral) advertising or other targeted content. 

We do not control third-party tracking technologies or how third parties’ use them. If you have any questions about an advertisement or other targeted content, you should contact the responsible provider directly. 

## 3\. How do we use your information?

We may use information that we collect about you or that you provide to us, including any personal information:   

  * To present our Website and its contents to you.
  * To provide you with information, products, or services that you request from us.
  * To fulfill any other purpose for which you provide it.
  * To provide you with notices about your account, including purchase receipts and alerts.
  * To carry out our obligations and enforce our rights arising from any contracts entered into between you and us, including for payment or for billing and collection.
  * To notify you about changes to our Website or any products or services we offer or provide through it.
  * To allow you to participate in any interactive features on our Website.
  * To monitor and analyze trends, usage, and activities in connection with the Website and for marketing or advertising purposes.
  * To investigate and prevent fraudulent transactions, unauthorized access to the Website, and other illegal activities.
  * To personalize the Website content, features, or advertisements.
  * In any other way we may describe when you provide the information.
  * For any other purpose with your consent.

We may also use your information to contact you about our own and third parties’ goods and services that may be of interest to you. If you do not want us to use your information in this way, please adjust your user preferences in your account profile. For more information, see **"What choices do you have about how we use and disclose your information".**

We may use the information we have collected from you to allow us to display advertisements to our advertisers’ target audiences. Even though we do not disclose your personal information for these purposes without your consent, if you click on or otherwise interact with an advertisement, the advertiser may assume that you meet its target criteria. 

## 4\. With whom do we share your information?

We may disclose aggregated information about our users, and information that does not identify any individual, without restriction. 

We may disclose personal information that we collect or you provide as described in this privacy policy: 

  * To our subsidiaries and affiliates.
  * To contractors, service providers, and other third parties we use to support our business and who are bound by contractual obligations to keep personal information confidential and use it only for the purposes for which we disclose it to them.
  * To a buyer or other successor in the event of a merger, divestiture, restructuring, reorganization, dissolution, or other sale or transfer of some or all of the Company’s assets, whether as a going concerning or as part of bankruptcy, liquidation, or similar proceeding, in which personal information held by the Company about our Website users is among the assets transferred.
  * To third parties to market their products or services to you if you have not opted out of these disclosures. We contractually require these third parties to keep personal information confidential and use it only for the purposes for which we disclose it to them. For more information, see What choices do you have about how we use and disclose your information.
  * To fulfill the purpose for which you provide it.
  * For any other purpose disclosed by us when you provide the information.
  * With your consent.

We may also disclose your personal information:   

  * To comply with any court order, law, or legal process, including to respond to any government or regulatory request.
  * To enforce or apply our terms and other agreements, including for payment or for billing and collection purposes.
  * If we believe disclosure is necessary or appropriate to protect the rights, property, or safety of the Company, our users, or others. This includes exchanging information with other companies and organizations for the purposes of fraud protection and credit risk reduction.

## 5\. What choices do you have about how we use and disclose your information?

We strive to provide you with choices about the personal information you provide to us. We have created mechanisms to provide you with the following control over your information:   

  * **Tracking Technologies and Advertising**. You can set your browser to refuse all or some browser cookies, or to alert you when cookies are being sent. To learn how you can manage your Flash cookie settings, visit the Flash player settings page on Adobe’s website. To learn how you can manage your other cookies, visit [www.allaboutcookies.org/manage-cookies/](http://www.allaboutcookies.org/manage-cookies/.eu). If you disable or refuse cookies, please note that some parts of this Website may then be inaccessible or not function properly.
  * **Disclosure of Your Information for Third-Party Advertising**. If you do not want us to share your personal information with unaffiliated or non-agent third parties for promotional purposes, you can opt-out by deselecting any pre-checked preference at the time we give you the option or at any other time by sending us an email stating your request to _privacy@darkmediagroup.com_.
  * **Promotional Offers from the Company**. If you do not want to have your email address used by the Company to promote our own or third parties’ products or services, you can opt-out by deselecting any pre-checked preference at the time we give you the option or at any other time by sending us an email stating your request to _privacy@darkmediagroup.com_. If we have sent you a promotional email, you may send us a return email asking to be omitted from future email distributions or click on the “unsubscribe” link at the bottom of the email. This opt out does not apply to information provided to the Company because of a service purchase or other transactions.
  * **Targeted Advertising**. If you do not want us to use information that we collect or that you provide to us to deliver advertisements according to our advertisers’ target-audience preferences, you can opt-out by deselecting any pre-checked preference at the time we give you the option. You can also always send us an email stating your request to _privacy@darkmediagroup.com_. For this opt-out to function, you must have your browser set to accept browser cookies.

We do not control third parties’ collection or use of your information to serve interest-based advertising. But these third parties may provide you with ways to choose not to have your information collected or used in this way. 

## 6\. How do you access and correct your information?

You can review and change your personal information by logging into the Website and visiting your account profile page. 

You may also send us an email at _privacy@darkmediagroup.com_ to request access to, correct, or delete any personal information that you have provided to us. We cannot delete your personal information except by also deleting your account. We will not accommodate a request to change information if we believe the change would violate any law or legal requirement or cause the information to be incorrect. 

If you delete your user contributions from the Website, copies of your user contributions might remain viewable in cached and archived pages, or might have been copied or stored by other Website users. Our terms govern proper access and use of information provided on the Website, including user contributions. 

## 7\. How do we protect your personal information?

We have implemented measures designed to secure your personal information from accidental loss and from unauthorized access, use, change, and disclosure. All information you provide to us is stored on our secure servers behind firewalls. We encrypt all payment transactions using SSL technology. 

The safety and security of your information also depends on you. Where we have given you (or where you have chosen) a password for access to certain parts of our Website, you are responsible for keeping this password confidential. You must not to share your password with anyone. 

**Warning:** The transmission of information over the Internet is not completely secure. Although we do our best to protect your personal information, we cannot guarantee the security of your personal information transmitted to our Website. Any transmission of personal information is at your own risk. We are not responsible for circumvention of any privacy settings or security measures contained on the Website. 

## 8\. International Users (all users whom reside outside of the United States including Brazil)

This policy is intended to cover collection of information on or through our Website from residents of the United States. If you are visiting our Website from outside the United States, please be aware that your information may be transferred to, stored, and processed in the United States where our servers are located and our central database is operated. The data protection and other laws of the United States and other countries might not be as comprehensive as those in your country. Please be assured that we seek to take reasonable steps to make sure that your privacy is protected. By using our services, you understand that your information may be transferred to our facilities and those third parties with whom we share it as described in this policy. When you provide personal information to us through the services, you consent to the processing of your data in, and the transfer of your data to, the United States or any other country in which we or our affiliates, subsidiaries, or service providers host these services. 

## 9\. Do Not Track Policy

Do Not Track (“DNT”) is a privacy preference that you can set in your browser. DNT is a way for you to inform websites and services that you do not want certain information about your webpage visits collected over time and across websites or online services. We are committed to providing you with meaningful choices about the information we collect and that is why we provide you the ability to opt-out. But we do not recognize or respond to any DNT signals as the Internet industry works toward defining exactly what DNT means, what it means to comply with DNT, and a common approach to responding to DNT. For more information about DNT signals, you may visit [http:/www.allaboutdnt.com](http://www.allaboutdnt.com/). 

## 10\. Your California Privacy Rights

California Civil Code § 1798.83 permits users of our Website that are California residents to request certain information about our disclosure of personal information to third parties for their direct marketing purposes. To make this request, please send an email to _privacy@darkmediagroup.com_. 

Further, if you are a California resident and would like to opt-out from the disclosure of your personal information to any third party for marketing purposes, please contact us at _privacy@darkmediagroup.com_. Please be advised that if you opt-out from permitting your personal information to be shared, you may still receive selected officers directly from us in accordance with California law. 

## 11\. Links para outros sites

O site contém links para outros sites. Esteja ciente que nós não somos responsáveis pelo conteúdo ou práticas de privacidade desses outros sites. Nós recomendamos aos nossos usuários que estejam cientes quando deixam o nosso site e leiam as declarações de privacidade de qualquer outro site que coleta informações pessoalmente identificáveis. 

## 12\. Nenhum direito de terceiros

Esta política de privacidade não cria direitos exequíveis por terceiros ou exigem a divulgação de informações pessoais relativas aos usuários do site. 

## 13\. Alterações na Política de Privacidade

Publicaremos todas as alterações que fizermos na nossa Política de Privacidade nesta página. Se fizermos alterações materiais em como tratamos as suas informações pessoais, iremos notificá-lo por e-mail para o endereço identificado na sua conta ou através de um aviso sobre a página inicial do Site. Esta política identifica quando nós atualizamos em uma mensagem no topo da página. Você é responsável por certificar-se de que possui um endereço de e-mail atualizado e ativo, e que você frequentemente acesse nosso Site para verificar quaisquer alterações. 

## 14\. Informações de contato

Para perguntas ou comentários sobre esta política de privacidade e nossas práticas de privacidade, contate-nos: 

_Dark Media Group LLC  
501 Silverside Road, # 104   
Wilmington, Delaware 19809   
USA   
privacy@darkmediagroup.com_
